hippressurecooking.com 2019-12-04

# privacy policy ⋆ hip pressure cooking

**information we gather**  
what you give us: We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing your future visits, improving our website, and communicating with you.

For example, you provide information when you search for a something; submit a contact form; register for the website; provide information in your personal profile (or profiles, if you have more than one); communicate with us by phone, email, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire; post in the forums; leave feedback on a post or use other hip pressure cooking features. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name (or another person’s); content of emails to us; and your email address.

what is automatically recorded: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many websites, we use “cookies,” and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses the hip pressure cooking website.

Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login to hip pressure cooking; email address; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our website, including date and time (how you arrived, navigated through and exited hip pressure cooking); cookie number; and pages you have viewed. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. This information is collected in the interest of making the hip pressure cooking website work better for you.

A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit websites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at hip pressure cooking if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist. In addition, the United States Federal Trade Commission provides useful information about online privacy on its own website, http://www.privacy.ca.gov/. 

information to/from other sources: Third party advertisers may appear on our website from time to time. They may be able to detect that visitors to their website arrived via hip pressure cooking. However, we do not receive any information from these or other outside websites regarding your page views, clicks, purchases or any other information.

**yummy internet cookies  
**Cookies are tiny bits of information that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as your personalized profile.

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of hip pressure cooking’s website’s features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

**we do not share your information  
**The trust of our readers is important to us, and we are not in the business of selling your information to others. 

However, we may share your information for the following purposes:

We may compile anonymous demographic information about our readers for business purposes.

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of hip pressure cooking, our readers, or others. This may include exchanging information with civil authorities, other companies and organizations in order to protect hip pressure cooking from illegal activities. 

_We will not sell_ , rent, share, or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information from readers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**the security of your information  
**hip pressure cooking is committed to protecting the security of your personal information and maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that meet industry standards to guard your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. 

It is important for you to guard against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off the website when finished using a shared computer.

**  
third-party advertisers**  
The hip pressure cooking website may include third-party advertising and links to other websites. We do not provide any personally identifiable reader information to these advertisers or third-party websites. The rest of this section offers some examples as well as information on how to opt-out of their information collection practices.

Examples of third-party advertisers and advertising companies that serve advertising content directly to your browser on certain hip pressure cooking pages may include [Google Adsense](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/1348695?hl=en) or [Amazon](https://www.amazon.com/gp/dra/info). You can find out more about their information collection and use practices, including how to opt out of cookies and other collection techniques that they use, by clicking on the links to their websites in this paragraph.

These third-party websites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send (or “serve”) the advertisements that appear on our website directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. In addition, the Network Advertising Initiative offers useful information about Internet advertising companies (also called “ad networks” or “network advertisers”), including information about how to opt-out of their information collection.

**information access  
**Information You Can Access: hip pressure cooking gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with hip pressure cooking for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. Examples of data you can access at hip pressure cooking include your profile information and forum posts. This list will change and expand as our website evolves.  
**  
you choose whether to provide information**  
You can always choose not to provide information, although it is needed to make a post, start a topic, upload a picture or to take advantage of such hip pressure cooking features as your personal profile. Consequently, if you choose not to provide information on this website, you will be unable to use features of the hip pressure cooking websit.

You can add or update certain information on pages such as your profile. When you update information, we may keep a copy of the prior version for our records.

**  
how we use your email address**  
Occasionally, we send emails to our readers in the form of a newsletter or announcements.

**Conditions of Use, Notices and Revisions  
**If you choose to visit hip pressure cooking, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law in Italy. If you have any concern about privacy at hip pressure cooking, please contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#84edeae2ebc4ecedf4f4f6e1f7f7f1f6e1e7ebebefedeae3aae7ebe9 "Reply To: Pressure Cooker Food Exploded!") with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it.

Our website is growing, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may email periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, though you should still check our website frequently to see reports on the latest changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

**NOTE FOR INTERNATIONAL READERS  
**By visiting hip pressure cooking you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Please note the following additional agreement:

I agree to the collection, use and processing of the personal information I provide to hip pressure cooking for the purposes of organization and administration. By submitting my personal information to hip pressure cooking, I also agree that my information may be accessed and used by hip pressure cooking its employees and agents, and will be transferred to countries that are not regarded as having adequate data protection, including to our web server which is located in the United States. I agree to notify [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) of any change to my personal information, including making any requests to check, delete or correct my personal information, so that it is accurate and current. I understand that the majority of the data requested during registration is necessary for administrative and planning purposes, and that the failure to provide this information may prevent my registration from being properly processed.
